My name is David Andre and here's week
in the life of a European villager in
New York City.
[Music]
>> Yeah. I don't know how this is a real
civilization, you know? It's like random
[__] happening.
>> Anything you got I could do for you guys
may need, you can't get.
>> Hm. You need anything you can't get?
>> No.
>> Okay. Stay cool. All right.
>> Yeah. Be safe.
>> That's such a good line, bro. You need
anything you can't get. What a banger
[__] sentence, bro.
>> It's time to make
[Music]
>> I'm seeing a lot of ads in New York City
for AI companies. I haven't seen one in
Europe. Why do you think that is?
>> I think it's way more entrepreneurial.
People are way more aggressive here.
They're willing to drop 50K on a
billboard on a building. You know, they
just don't care.
[Music]
>> So, we're headed to the Rockefeller
Center.
>> Yes.
>> Would you say he's one of your
inspirations in business?
>> I mean, he's definitely one of the
greatest entrepreneurs of all time.
There's a great biography, the Titan.
It's like 36 hours. I listened to it
twice.
>> What are some strategies you picked up
from him?
>> Making sure you know where your money is
going. The competitors, he outco
competed. He just hired them internally
and gave them stock. Also, he built a
product. People forget his product was
standard oil. It was a reliable quality
oil that let people light up their lamps
and it allowed millions of people to
work at night, you know, without using
candles.
I'm trying to analyze why is America
ahead cuz I feel like Czech Republic,
Poland have so many things that New York
doesn't have. We need to bring in the
ambition, the thinking big into Europe.
This place is gone. Like I'm not better.
I think New York in 10 20 years would be
a [__] hole. It already is a [__] hole.
Let's be honest. Like get spent on the
streets. Shit's crazy, right? Start
spreading the news.
I'm leaving today.
I want to be
>> I see all of the parts in the business.
So I see like okay, it's maybe like a
P3. You know, there's like 10 other
things that are more important. So kind
of keeping on track, making sure they're
actually working on the most important
things. So, how do you know David?
>> Following David on YouTube, join new
society.
>> What made you join the new society?
>> Life is about learning. AI is about
learning.
>> David's doing a good thing. Excited to
learn from it, man.
>> Okay. I started because I watched him
build an agent and I'm automating in
fashion design. So, that's what
interested me and I joined the group.
But the most coolest thing is the guys
that uh I meet like they're a really
good support group.
[Music]
Bro, this Minecraft building, what the
[__]
>> So, Jack, why are we in New York?
>> So, I'm in New York. Couple of reasons.
We got the NE10 event tomorrow and then
we've got the AI agent battle on
Thursday, Nate HK, and it's going to be
a badass, man. Looking forward to it.
When you leave Dubai and you come to a
different state, there's like this air
of criminality.
>> Like when you walk, you're like you just
feel that you're one one left turn from
getting like rubbed or something.
>> What did you watch the whole Morocco
vlog?
>> Yeah, dude. That [__] was so far. I
watched it a couple times.
>> Bro, you have no idea how much how much
time went into that.
>> It was so good.
I don't want to sleep
in a row.
>> Some nice artwork, bro.
>> It's AI generated.
>> Isn't Veil just a glorified to-doist
app? Why do you believe in it so much?
>> Because I know where it's headed. I know
why I built it and I know that something
like this must exist. Productivity is a
multiund billion industry. So a tool
like this will exist purely thinking
from first principles. So I don't know
like maybe it's just delusion but for me
like I know I can build something that
only few people in the world can even
imagine.
>> Yo yo.
>> So welcome to the humble New York City
penthouse. We have a view of Empire
State Building. Over there we have the
Hudson River.
>> Nice. So how much
>> this place?
>> Yeah. 10.5K
>> a month?
>> No, a week.
>> Yeah, 10.5K a week. So, the funny thing
is like for this price in Dubai, you
would live like the king basically.
>> Okay, this is a sick view.
>> And then here we have another room with
a standing desk and triple monitor and
another sick view of some skyscrapers.
Yeah. So, here we have vectal as of
August 2025. new feature workflows, our
internal way of automating different
processes. So, this is the V1, you know,
obviously we're going to improve this
and extend this over time. We're going
to add Gmail. We're going to add all the
Google products, all kinds of different
triggers and actions. And this, I think,
will be one of the main things that
makes Vex unique. Currently, the MR is
10.05.
So, basically, we hit 10K MR again. So
if you remember in the Switzerland vlog
we crossed that but the problem is that
was like the from the initial hype but
also a lot of people joined for the
wrong reasons. Now however we have way
more power users and we have this custom
metric that we call a use which is
active paying power user which is a
person who is not only paying obviously
but also using it at least 4 days a
week. Any of the APUs can book a call
with me 15-minute call give any of the
feedback and this is really the secret.
is like talking to the customer.
[Music]
So, we have five stickers. We're going
to deploy them across Manhattan. Whoever
finds them, take a photo with the
sticker and you will get lifetime access
to Vector Pro. First one is going here.
Just take a photo, message me on IG.
You'll get lifetime access to Vector
Pro.
Vector Pro. There it is. Central Park.
[Music]
This is a great spot for the Beal
sticker.
[Music]
you know your theory of the best LLMs
will have you know the biggest data
centers the best talent and the most
money
>> why does Apple fall into that category
but it doesn't have the best LLM
>> it's a great question the seuite
executives are not locked in They have
nothing in terms of AI models or
architecture.
>> Grock caught up very quickly. You don't
think they can catch up?
>> No, because Apple is a big ass [__]
bureaucracy.
>> So, it's it's not easy to turn around
[Music]
fields. you running and on and on.
Sometimes you turn around and see me
falling far behind.
>> You know a lot of people that are doing
N10 agents and AI automations. Do you
think that's a good way to like get
started with making money with AI if
you're not technical?
>> Definitely. like it's much easier than
writing custom code and it's a level
ahead of CHBT and just you know using AI
tools
>> showing each feature especially the new
ones how to use them what you can do
with them stuff like
[Music]
So, we're here the NSA building.
No windows. Nobody knows anything about
it, but we're about to get inside.
Yeah. So, look at this. Anthropic is
destroying all the other companies in
terms of retaining talent. People are
leaving Deep Find and OpenAI and they're
joining Antropic and they have the
highest retention of AI researchers out
of any company. So, everybody wants to
work at Enthropic.
>> Do you? No. Yeah. will be here.
Washington Square, Empire State
Building, tons of diversity, tons of
culture.
Now, we might need to import some more
immigrants into Europe.
>> It's the biggest elevator I've ever
seen, bro.
>> What a [__] elevator. That's crazy.
>> There's like the TEFL or TOEFL radio
tower outside of
[Music]
Are you doing another vlog?
>> Another vlog. I'm in love with your
vlog.
>> Really?
>> I say they're flopping, bro.
>> Why am I not giving a presentation? My
presentations are worldrenowned.
>> All right. Well, I welcome everyone.
We're excited to show you some of the
new features in N.
>> What we can see on the screen here is
some pretty simple AI agent that we're
probably all pretty familiar with. So if
I wanted to evaluate this model, what
are some things that I might want to
evaluate against? So represented in this
graph, red means that it failed a
particular test. Green means that it
passed.
>> So what are your thoughts on the new
NA10 updates so far?
>> Yeah, so there's a lot of quality of
life updates, simplification,
scalability, also the evals. So yeah,
NA10 is a big inspiration and we will
still continue using it because it
allows you to automate and connect
multiple different softwares, right?
>> There is no typical team right now.
Okay.
>> Yo, it's cold as [__] bro.
>> Yo,
essentially just
>> How's the exit going?
>> My brother-in-law uses now.
>> Really?
>> Yeah. I I put him on. I'm like, dude,
just use this. He's like a college kid.
Dude, you got to advertise your phone
features now.
>> Oh, mobile app. Yeah.
>> The stuff you're showing me. I was like,
>> yeah. Yeah. So,
>> no one knows about this. Vectal as a
mobile app works 10 times better.
Really? Vector? Yes.
>> Oh [__]
>> Yo, the robot is down.
>> Yo, that's crazy.
>> Stop resisting.
>> Were you saying we need some percentage
of that?
>> I think I think you helped. We both
helped that a little bit. I think part
of your part of the story, man. Listen,
let's pitch this to y. I get 1%. You get
1%. It's only fair, bro.
>> Yeah. I got to say if we can arm wrestle
right now for 1%
>> bench press competition.
>> I'm gonna I'm gonna do everything I can
to win. I don't know.
>> Okay, we're not going to show it to
Jack. Any like secrets you have, you
know? Can you defeat it?
>> Secrets I have.
>> I never imagine.
>> Well, hey, here's the thing. Here's the
thing.
>> You know how they've been talking a lot
about rag, you know, and when you think
of rag, you think of like vector
database rag.
>> I might not take that approach.
>> Interesting.
>> I mean, we got like large context
winners. We're living in 2025. If you
don't have to chunk it up, don't chunk
it up. Every everyone's looking to make
money with these a automations. All you
got to do, you don't got to start an
agency. You just have to be on a AIA
game show where you build agents and
then that's that's the money-making
opportunity right there.
>> Yeah,
>> that's the secret.
>> That's the secret.
>> That's the secret. I guess so.
>> Funny. Everyone always asks what's like
the secret like cuz David uploads
consistently, right? We have joke.
What's the secret? You know what's the
secret to uploading? What's the secret
to getting fit? And it's like always the
obvious answer.
We're headed to the Jack Nate battle at
NA10. You know, this NA10 event really
goes to show how important the community
is, I think.
>> Yes. Like the N10 team is great. You
know, Dylan, Max, Yan, like we even get
offers from their competitors and we
still turn them down because the NA10 is
not only the best product right now, but
also they have a great team that work
with the creators and, you know, make
trips like this possible. Let's get to
our first challenge. You're going to be
building a question and answer bot.
Dpping right into the flow. He's adding
a form trigger probably so he can ingest
those PDF documents into a rag.
>> You predicted it on the vlog yesterday.
>> Yeah,
>> you said it for dag.
>> I did.
>> What happened was I was using opus for
with thinking and sometimes it thinks,
sometimes it doesn't.
>> And when it doesn't think, it outputs a
different variable for its answer. So
when it didn't think, I got zero points
because it it evaluated the wrong
variable.
>> So then you change to what? Sonet. No, I
mean mid mid evaluation I couldn't
change.
>> Oh, okay.
>> And I I I did. Yeah. So, that was a
little rough.
>> So, would you use like GBD5 instead if
you could do it again?
>> Probably would have gone with like 03.
>> Yeah. I wanted like a big reasoning
model
>> behind the scenes.
>> Thank you. I appreciate it.
>> So, this is where the battle will
happen, the finale.
[Music]
We're here midway. Nate is winning, but
it's not over, right?
>> So, it's a pretty close game.
>> Yeah.
>> And the second challenge, there's more
points and it's a trivia challenge where
we've got a humanoid robot and they have
to control the robot to go from the
start line to the finish line just with
N. Yeah. Yeah. So, Nitn is a tool that
the robot consumes to give it the answer
for the trivia.
>> So, this is cool to see. It's the
world's first AI Asian eport. Imagine if
like 5 years there's like 100,000
people, you know, at these events.
>> My vision one day I want to give someone
a million dollars for winning an AI
challenge. It might be you in future.
Would you be want to be a future
contestant?
>> Sure.
>> Awesome. Awesome.
>> Why not?
>> Such a big prize.
>> Yeah. We got 10 G's on the line right
here.
>> 10K cash, right?
>> 10K cash. Yeah.
>> Let's explore the backstage. So, here we
have a bunch of gear.
Camera gear, plugs,
cables,
gimbals. So, this is a producer room,
makeup room. Where's my makeup lady?
Okay. Anyways, there's another set here
with a diffuser lights. Oh, the robot.
We got the robot again.
>> He's getting ready because um
>> it'll be recorded as well.
>> Yes. Sensor blow.
>> The N10 bot service
>> type [__]
>> Yeah. So I guess introduce yourself and
the robot.
>> I'm the founder of GA which is the
company that makes the humanoids and the
goal is to have another fleet a larger
fleet to help with factory talent.
>> Where do you think like 5 to 10 years if
you had to paint the picture? What will
the world look like? the world like you
know you have when you divide up things
economically you have land labor and
capital labor will no longer exist it'll
just be capital right so like you'll be
able to generate untold amount of wealth
right this is like charg but in a
physical form
>> so if the robot replies with the correct
[Music]
So this is interesting because Jack is
doing a completely different thing than
I would do.
>> I would not have ch the system prompt. I
would write the system pro myself. My
competitive nature is trying to not
crash out because I wish I could.
measure my skills against them.
>> But what's the first law of the three
laws of robotics?
>> A robot may not injure a human being.
>> It's 100% absolutely correct. Step
forward.
>> Nate Herk, you are the winner of the
first ever Agentic Arena. Let's give the
man some cash.
>> What are we doing with the money, Nate?
Yeah. Um, I think we're going to donate
it.
>> We're going to match you. We're going to
match 10 grand to charity from NN. We're
doubling the prize.
>> What's your advice for like new startup
founders? Because you had a great year
with N10, massive growth,
>> but it's, you know, five, six years in
the making. So, what's your advice for
startup founders?
>> I think it's probably mainly to like do
stuff you're actually excited about in
the end and actually kind of if you
believe in it, just keep on pushing like
in the end. Like if you would have
stopped like a year or two ago like it
was always going well but like if you
want to have this this kind of outsized
kind of impact and this kind of outside
success you like it it takes time like
everything you're doing is not happening
overnight you have to invest a lot of
time resource and you have to you have
to believe in it and if you give up too
fast then you you're never going to
build anything amazing in the end
>> drawing a lot of inspiration for my own
startup you know obviously
>> I'm pretty good we just reached 10k MR
so
>> nice
>> you know not as big as n but
>> and also after we reach 10k like the
growth from there was took a long time
really just like there. I think the last
12 months you go like 9x in AR but it
took a long time to actually get there.
So 10k is already achievement.
>> I I like your like focus on the product
and uh speaking with some of your team
they said like the you know series C was
also to kind of protect the decision-
making right so you can you don't have
to face out outside pressures so you can
fully focus on the best what best
decision of the product. Now we can take
more risks and have the opportunity to
kind of
>> do something that's just just exciting
and cool. But at the same time, we we
still focus pretty much kind of trying
to build a sustainable company like just
trying to become kind of not be reliant
on investor money like moving forward
like we we can become profitable if you
want to.
>> Why New York and not SF?
>> Because the time it's like having like 6
hours was kind of doable but having like
9 hours to have like more time to play.
[Music]
an 11minute tutorial. Pure se silver
lines if the heli starts crashing so I
can take control
>> or if we get a female pilot
if you look into my rear clutches
engaged.
>> So I watched a quick tutorial and low
key I know how to fly the heli now. So
we're at the heli spot and I'm going to
deploy another vector sticker. So,
whoever finds it, take a photo, message
me on IG
>> and you will receive lifetime access to
vector control.
>> Yeah. So, here we're deploying the last
sticker.
Val and Bitcoin are the two main
technologies of the last 20 years. So,
we're going to put them together.
[Music]
I
[Applause]
swept away. I'm stol
[Music]
face it all
together.
I have the utmost contempt for people
who play lottery tickets and scratch
offs cuz like it's not only gambling but
it's almost like you're trying to cheat
the rules of the universe trying to get
something for nothing. I think in the
last 80 years nothing apart from
technology is better.
World is not more safe.
The culture has declined. There's no
progress in anything else apart from
technology. Because if you look at the
videos from Europe, 20s, 30s, 40s, any
city, look, even the architecture,
Empire State Building was built in the
20s. That's like 100 years ago. So in
the last 80 years, the only thing we
have is technology, whether it's
smartphones, the internet, computers,
AI, everything else is worse.
>> Didn't seem like it was a winning
combination.
>> Scratching his [__] ass, bro. Crazy.
But do you think that like this wealth
disparity we have right now is better if
you want to be in the top 1%. Cuz you
have more technology, more
opportunities, more money to make than
ever before.
>> That is true. Like if you are an
overachiever, you can use the technology
to get ahead. But society as a whole is
worse off. In the 30s, it took 8 months,
eight monthly paychecks to buy a house.
That is impossible in every single
country in the world right now.
Inflation has ruined
>> the ability for young people to acquire
homes and all standards of living except
for technology are way worse.
>> Nothing ever like money how it blows in
the wind. Got me taking medicine. This
is not vitamin. I thought that we were
meant to be struck out.
So, we're at Grand Central, which is the
legendary train station in New York
City. And I've seen this in so many
documentaries about Cornelius
Vanderbilt, Tom Scott, Andrew Carnegie,
and the battles of the railways in the
1800s of USA. So, it kind of feels
surreal being here. Like to me, this is
like way better than Time Square or any
of these mainstream attractions. This is
a legendary piece of history in the
modern era of business.
[Music]
It's amazing how two big towers can fall
at near free fall speeds, you know. It's
amazing how that works. I like Newton
would be pissed low key.
Shadow done.
>> Shadow done.
>> Oh, it's not bad.
>> It's warm.
>> Yo, they're all waving, bro. David
Andre, you have any crazy cop stories?
>> Oh my god. Yeah,
>> a lot of them. Eight years. I did two
Westpack tours. Uh did the Mediterranean
through Australia and New Zealand. Um I
was stationed in Okinawa, Japan as well.
>> And I was stationed in Guantano Bay for
a year at sunset. Beautiful.